mlsu.ac.in 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy :: Mohanlal Sukhadia Univerity, Udaipur

**Privacy Statement**

At the Mohanlal Sukhadia University we recognize that your personal privacy is a serious and important issue and we support the principle of protecting privacy on the Internet within the context of current Indian legislation.

This privacy policy explains how we treat your personal information. By using the Mohanlal Sukhadia University web site you consent to the collection and use of your personal information in accordance with this policy. Though the policy has been developed to take account of changes in Internet technology it is subject to change and any such changes will only be notified on this page.

**What information is collected?**

In order to use the main web site at the Mohanlal Sukhadia University, you are currently not required to register or provide any personal information about yourself. Any personal information collected from visitors to our website is on a purely voluntary basis, however by supplying the information you are consenting to the University keeping it for a reasonable period of time and using it for the purposes set out below.

On occasions we may ask you to provide some limited personal information about yourself to participate in services such as the Alumni email directory or the University Contact Information and Online Faculty facility. This information may include your name, title, institutional affiliation, address, telephone number and email address. It may be stored electronically or manually by the University.

When you view our web pages as with most other websites, our web servers build logs of activity which contain information about your location in the world and even your computers IP address. In addition on some pages small visible graphics are used to build and enhance this logging system.

**What we do with the information?**

Any personal information that you provide to us will only be used for the purpose stated at the time we request it. We will not sell, license or trade your personal information to others. We do not provide your personal information to direct marketing companies or other such organisations.

Personal information provided by you, and any other information relating to you, will be held by the Mohanlal Sukhadia University and may be used for its own marketing purposes, or occasionally shared with other organisations in the prevention of fraud.

Using the logging data we analyze demographic and other statistical information about user behavior to analyze the popularity and effectiveness of our site. In performing such analysis and in the course of our business we will only ever disclose such information in an aggregated form that is not capable of identifying an individual user.

Any questions?

If you have any queries or concerns about privacy on the Mohanlal Sukhadia University website please contact us at 

counsellor@mlsu.ac.in
